So  this
Indian  company
called  Smolest
.A .A
have  released
in  service
for  real
time  text
to
speak  conversion.
So  it
gives  very
human  sounding
voice  instead
of  very
robotic.
We  can
test  their
demo  by
going  to
their  dashboard
over  here.
So  you
can  see
I  page
just  show
you.
So  they
give  very
a  lot
of  options
to  choose
from.
So  there
are  mostly
American  and
English  accent
as  well
as  language.
We  can
choose  the
language  over
here.
So  I
will  just
test  one
of  the
other  super
this  voice.
And  if
I  see
this,  I
have  this
English  text
now.
If  I
click  generate.
The  sun
sets  over
the  quiet
village.
Casting  a
warm  glow
across  the
fields.
You  can
see  it
sounds  very
proper  human
like  instead
of  robotic.
Now  I
will  just
try  with
some  Hindi
text.
Surah  shandh
ghan  ka
yumpad  halta
hai.
Ketu  par
ig  gha.
Ram  chamak
bi  khe
rta  hai.
Ya  is
very  good
actually.